http://www.mazdausa.com/site/privacy

Apply For Financing
Already know the car you want?  Let us help you get a quote.
#DiscoverMazda
Improving the lives of drivers,by creating a better vehicle.
Mazda Collection
Go to MyMazda to enjoy the full benefits of being a Mazda Owner.
Confirm
To view Your California Privacy Rights, click here.
Information Regarding Privacy Practices
This Privacy Policy describes how Mazda North American Operations (also, us or we) collects, uses and shares information about you through our websites, mobile applications, and other online services that link to or incorporate this Privacy Policy (the Online Services). This includes information you provide to us, as well as information we may collect about your website usage patterns.
The Online Services may provide links to other Mazda North American Operations websites or third-party websites not controlled by Mazda, such as Mazda Dealer sites, third-party vehicle purchase sites or third-party product review sites. Any information collected by those websites is subject to those sites’ privacy policies, and we recommend that you check the privacy policies of those sites before providing any information to them.
How We Collect Information
The Online Services collect information that you provide when requesting products, services or information through the Online Services including, but not limited to, your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number and vehicle identification number (VIN). This may include when you request a vehicle brochure, enter a contest, request direct dealer contact (e.g., request a quote, contact dealer or request a test drive) or create a MyMazda account. We also collect any information that you include in emails you send to us. If you have a MyMazda account, you may update, review or correct your account information by logging into your MyMazda account.
We and our service providers may also over time use cookies to collect information about your usage of the Online Services and third-party websites that have a business relationship with our service providers. A cookie is a small data file that is sent to your browser from a website's servers and stored on your computer's hard drive, and is used to store information such as the name of your Internet service provider, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the website that referred you, your general geographic location, the pages you request, and the dates and times of those requests. These cookies simulate a continuous connection to the website and permit us to provide you with a more personalized experience, such as making it more convenient for you to find information that may have interested you in a previous session. We also use cookies to measure website activity and generate statistics that allow us to improve the services we provide through the Online Services.
Any website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.)
We do not currently respond to web browser do not track signals or other mechanisms that provide a method to opt out of the collection of information about online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services. If we do so in the future, we will describe how we do so in the Privacy Policy. For information about do not track, visit www.allaboutdnt.org.
We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising, through which some of our service providers that use cookies to collect information about your usage of the Online Services allow you to opt out of certain uses of your information. For more information about how to opt out, click here.
How We Use Information
The information that we collect may be used to provide you with the products, services or information you request, deliver marketing communications or promotional materials that may be of interest to you through various channels (such as through email, on the Online Services, or on third-party websites you visit), improve the services we provide you, measure website activity and generate statistics, improve the usefulness of customer visits, and customize your experience on the Online Services. We also may combine any of the information, both personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable, that we collect through the Online Services and offline.
How We Share Information
We may share information that we collect with our corporate partners and affiliates. We also may share this information with service providers and agents for use on behalf of Mazda North American Operations (e.g., to provide operational and support functions, to deliver marketing communications or promotional materials that may be of interest to you) and authorized Mazda Dealers so that we may better serve your needs. In addition, we may share this information with business partners to provide you with services or offers that you request.
Aside from the above, your personally identifiable information is never sold to or shared with any third party for that party's independent use.
Security
We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to help us protect the personally identifiable information you provide through the Online Services. However, no security systems are 100% impenetrable, and we cannot guarantee the security of our databases or the Online Services, nor can we guarantee that the information you provide will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.
Children’s Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personally identifiable information about a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new version to the Online Services. If we make any revisions that materially change the ways in which we use or share the information you previously provided through the Online Services, we will give you the opportunity to consent to such changes before applying them to this information.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about the Online Services or this Privacy Policy, please contact us here.
Copyright Notice
© 2016 Mazda North American Operations. All rights reserved. All text, images, graphics, animation, videos, music, sounds and other materials on the Online Services are subject to the copyrights and other intellectual property rights of Mazda Motor of America, Inc., its affiliated companies and its licensors. Mazda Motor of America, Inc. owns the copyrights in the selection, coordination and arrangement of the materials on the Online Services. These materials may not be copied for commercial use or distribution, nor may these materials be modified or reposted to other web sites.
Effective Date: September 10, 2018
1
MSRP excludes taxes, title, license fees and $945 destination charge (Alaska $990). Vehicle shown may be priced higher. Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
2
MSRP excludes tax, title, license fees and $1,100 destination charge (Alaska $1,145). Vehicle shown may be priced higher. Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
3
MSRP excludes taxes, title, license fees and $1,100 destination charge (Alaska $1,145). Vehicle shown may be priced higher. Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
4
MSRP excludes tax, title, license fees and $1,045 destination charge (Alaska $1,090). Vehicle shown may be priced higher. Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
5
MSRP excludes tax, title, license fees and $945 destination charge (Alaska $990). Vehicle shown may be priced higher. Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
6
MSRP excludes taxes, title, license fees and $945 destination charge (Alaska $990). Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
7
MSRP excludes taxes, title, license fees and $920 destination charge (Alaska $965). Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
1
MSRP excludes taxes, title, license fees and $945 destination charge (Alaska $990). Vehicle shown may be priced higher. Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
2
MSRP excludes tax, title, license fees and $1,100 destination charge (Alaska $1,145). Vehicle shown may be priced higher. Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
3
MSRP excludes taxes, title, license fees and $1,100 destination charge (Alaska $1,145). Vehicle shown may be priced higher. Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
4
MSRP excludes tax, title, license fees and $1,045 destination charge (Alaska $1,090). Vehicle shown may be priced higher. Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
5
MSRP excludes tax, title, license fees and $945 destination charge (Alaska $990). Vehicle shown may be priced higher. Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
6
MSRP excludes taxes, title, license fees and $945 destination charge (Alaska $990). Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
7
MSRP excludes taxes, title, license fees and $920 destination charge (Alaska $965). Actual dealer price will vary. See dealer for complete details.
